<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Static News</string>
    <string name="hacker">Lifehacker.com</string>
    <string-array name="title">
        <item>The Best iOS Walkie Talkie Apps to Use Instead of Apple\'s</item>
        <item>Don\'t Answer Unsolicited Calls from Apple</item>
        <item>Here\'s Everything Apple Changed with MacBooks Today</item>
        <item>Where to Buy the Discontinued 12-Inch MacBook</item>
        <item>Google Play Pass or Apple Arcade: Which App Subscription Service Is Better?</item>
        <item>Listen to This July 4th Playlist If You Have Complicated Feelings About America</item>
        <item>Why Some USB-C Headphone Dongles Don\'t Work</item>
        <item>How to Back up Your Personal Data on iOS and Android</item>
        <item>Update to iOS 12.4 Right Now to Block New Vulnerabilities</item>
        <item>Use Your iPad as a Secondary Display in macOS Catalina</item>
        <item>Uninstall These Eight Browser Extensions That Stole Data from Millions</item>
        <item>How to Use Faster Context Menus in the Latest iOS 13 and iPadOS 13 Beta</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc">
        <item>Apple has temporarily disabled the Apple Watch\'s Walkie-Talkie app after discovering a bug that could have
            let others listen in on conversations. While Apple says no incidents of eavesdropping have been reported,
            the app is disabled until the vulnerability is...
        </item>
        <item>Recently, you may have received an urgent-sounding voicemail from \"Apple,\" claiming your \"financial activity\" on your devices was at stake...
        </item>
        <item>Apple made some big announcements today regarding the fate of its entry-level laptops. The company has
            discontinued the 12-inch MacBook (RIP), the non-Retina display MacBook Air, and made it impossible to buy a
            MacBook Pro without a (controversial) Touch Bar...
        </item>
        <item>Apple made some big changes to its MacBook lineup today-including axing the super-portable 12-inch
            MacBook, the entry-level MacBook of choice for many. While you can’t buy Apple\'s MacBook from its official
            store anymore, you still have a few options to get yo...
        </item>
        <item>Subscriptions are all the rage, and it’s easy to see why. Everyone loves an a la carte model for
            content—see Netflix, et al—where you can just pay a single reasonable monthly fee for unlimited access to a
            body of stuff you’re interested in, be it documentarie...
        </item>
        <item>If you find \"Fight the Power\" more patriotic than \"God Bless the U.S.A.,\" if you think it\'s one thing to
            love America but it\'s another to act like its obsessive boyfriend, then we have an Independence Day playlist
            for you. We have easy barbecue jams like “Par...
        </item>
        <item>Ever since Apple ditched the iPhone\'s headphone jack, getting your old headphones to work with newer
            smartphones has become a messy issue. Plenty of Android models still have 3.5mm audio jacks, but some, like
            Samsung\'s upcoming Galaxy Note 10, have followed A...
        </item>
        <item>Phones break or get lost all the time, but that doesn\'t mean you have to lose your personal data when and
            if that happens. In the video above, I go over the basics of backing up your Apple and Android devices. Read
            more...
        </item>
        <item>Most of you are running iOS 12. And that\'s a good thing, because you\'re getting a speedier experience with
            as many patched bugs and vulnerabilities as possible. It\'s especially important, too, given that Google
            researchers recently disclosed six serious iOS v...
        </item>
        <item>One of the neater features you’ll find in macOS Catalina-one that definitely got my attention, at least is
            Apple\'s new \"Sidecar\" mode. Like a tiny seat attached to a larger motorcycle, Sidecar allows you to link
            your iPad to your Mac and use it as a secondary...
        </item>
        <item>A massive data leak was recently discovered by cybersecurity researcher Sam Jidali, revealing private
            information for 45 major companies and millions of individuals. Dubbed \"DataSpii\" by Jidali and his team,
            the leak was perpetrated by innocent-looking Chro...
        </item>
        <item>The fourth iOS 13 and iPadOS beta has rolled out for developers, and while there are the usual list of
            changes and bug-fixes in Beta 4, one of the more interesting tweaks is a much more responsive Context Menu
            that you\'ll be able to pull up on any device runn
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="link">
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/the-best-ios-walkie-talkie-apps-to-use-instead-of-apple-1836286572</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/dont-answer-unsolicited-calls-from-apple-1836382309</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/heres-everything-apple-changed-with-macbooks-today-1836218640</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/where-to-buy-the-discontinued-12-inch-macbook-1836220069</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/google-play-pass-or-apple-arcade-which-app-subscriptio-1836890417</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/listen-to-this-july-4th-playlist-if-you-have-complicate-1836044367</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/why-some-usb-c-headphone-dongles-dont-work-1836316524</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/how-to-back-up-your-personal-data-on-ios-and-android-1836318995</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/update-to-ios-12-4-right-now-to-block-new-vulnerabiliti-1836856944</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/use-your-ipad-as-a-secondary-display-in-macos-catalina-1836053578</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/uninstall-these-eight-browser-extensions-that-stole-dat-1836539093</item>
        <item>https://lifehacker.com/how-to-use-faster-context-menus-in-the-latest-ios-13-an-1836501619</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="image">
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--ohcMViHR--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/kxq7cphmmgrxz9z6oggd.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--e8E_fCgS--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/yewhhkgtgv6cxo2quwuy.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--bJU-eZaK--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/haj9n7ahqrhdkji8dyoc.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--Wx7-oUpc--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/j5mwmupcbylnlvai1wzb.png
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--L69EVV9U--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/rhlgyq3trw5q77jlc4zw.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--cTWllBkd--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/gmnf8vkclt9uyipcmdzv.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--q1Ovi3Uj--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/iln6mvgcm3o7vobvozxi.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--UJHvU5wJ--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/dbpkbwxytvy3ozyl2ryd.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--dA-mihpo--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/rq6gynmki0vrk5zlvt5q.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--GgJvxzej--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/iohdho9kq9kvyvtztlgm.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--dHBECuHg--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/mia9ot2zvqfdnwflrwt7.jpg
        </item>
        <item>
            https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--CbqbEIUE--/c_fill,fl_progressive,g_center,h_900,q_80,w_1600/g5q1ilopm6tc3m9wtqhn.jpg
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="published">
        <item>2019-07-11T22:00:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-15T21:00:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-09T19:10:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-09T20:30:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-08-02T14:16:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-03T14:00:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-12T18:15:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-15T17:30:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-31T19:15:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-04T14:00:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-19T20:15:00Z</item>
        <item>2019-07-18T21:25:00Z</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="content">
        <item>Apple has temporarily disabled the Apple Watchs Walkie-Talkie app after discovering a bug that could have
            let others listen in on conversations. While Apple says no incidents of eavesdropping have been reported,
            the app is disabled until the vulnerability is...
        </item>
        <item>Recently, you may have received an urgent-sounding voicemail from Apple, claiming your financial activity
            on your devices was at stake.\r\nDont worryyour Apple accounts are fine and the companyisnt calling users to
            personally warn them about supposed suspicious...
        </item>
        <item>Apple made some big announcements today regarding the fate of its entry-level laptops. The company has
            discontinued the 12-inch MacBook (RIP), the non-Retina display MacBook Air, and made it impossible to buy a
            MacBook Pro without a (controversial) Touch Bar...
        </item>
        <item>Apple made some big changes to its MacBook lineup todayincluding axing the super-portable 12-inch MacBook,
            the entry-level MacBook of choice for many. While you cant buy Apples MacBook from its official store
            anymore, you still have a few options to get your...
        </item>
        <item>Subscriptions are all the rage, and its easy to see why. Everyone loves an a la carte model for contentsee
            Netflix, et alwhere you can just pay a single reasonable monthly fee for unlimited access to a body of stuff
            youre interested in, be it documentaries, 9...
        </item>
        <item>If you find Fight the Power more patriotic than God Bless the U.S.A., if you think its one thing to love
            America but its another to act like its obsessive boyfriend, then we have an Independence Day playlist for
            you. We have easy barbecue jams like Party in t...
        </item>
        <item>Ever since Apple ditched the iPhones headphone jack, getting your old headphones to work with newer
            smartphones has become a messy issue. Plenty of Android models still have 3.5mm audio jacks, but some, like
            Samsungs upcoming Galaxy Note 10, have followed App...
        </item>
        <item>Phones break or get lost all the time, but that doesnt mean you have to lose your personal data when and
            if that happens. In the video above, I go over the basics of backing up your Apple and Android
            devices.\r\nQuick Fix is a new video series where I tackle yo...
        </item>
        <item>Most of you are running iOS 12. And thats a good thing, because youre getting a speedier experience with
            as many patched bugs and vulnerabilities as possible. Its especially important, too, given that Google
            researchers recently disclosed six serious iOS vuln...
        </item>
        <item>One of the neater features youll find in macOS Catalinaone that definitely got my attention, at leastis
            Apples new Sidecar mode. Like a tiny seat attached to a larger motorcycle, Sidecar allows you to link your
            iPad to your Mac and use it as a secondary displ...
        </item>
        <item>A massive data leak was recently discovered by cybersecurity researcher Sam Jidali, revealing private
            information for 45 major companies and millions of individuals. Dubbed DataSpii by Jidali and his team, the
            leak was perpetrated by innocent-looking Chrome a...
        </item>
        <item>The fourth iOS 13 and iPadOS beta has rolled out for developers, and while there are the usual list of
            changes and bug-fixes in Beta 4, one of the more interesting tweaks is a much more responsive Context Menu
            that youll be able to pull up on any device runni...
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
